Finding aid for the William Bast papers LSC.2290
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Series 1. Television productions, 1960-2001
  - The First Olympics: Athens 1896 (NBC, 1984)
    - First draft teleplay, part two by William Bast, from a story by Charles Gary Allison and William Bast [annotated], undated (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - First draft teleplay, part one by William Bast, from a story by Charles Gary Allison and William Bast, May 23, 1983-June 22, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Revised first draft teleplay, part one by William Bast, from a story by Charles Gary Allison and William Bast, June 22, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - First draft teleplay, part two by William Bast, from a story by Charles Gary Allison and William Bast, June 22, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Revised first draft teleplay, part one by William Bast, from a story by Charles Gary Allison and William Bast, June 22, 1983-September 16, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous script pages by William Bast, from a story by Charles Gary Allison and William Bast [annotated], June 22, 1983-September 16, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Second revision of first draft teleplay, part one by William Bast, from a story by Charles Gary Allison and William Bast, September 16, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Second draft teleplay, part one by William Bast, from a story by Charles Gary Allison and William Bast [annotated], September 16, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Second revision of first draft teleplay, parts one and two, by William Bast, from a story by Charles Gary Allison and William Bast [annotated], September 16, 1983 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Second revision of first draft teleplay, part one by William Bast, from a story by Charles Gary Allison and William Bast [annotated], September 16, 1983 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Second draft teleplay, part two by William Bast, from a story by Charles Gary Allison and William Bast, September 23, 1983 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Second draft teleplay, part two by William Bast, from a story by Charles Gary Allison and William Bast [annotated], September 23, 1983 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Second draft teleplay, part two by William Bast, from a story by Charles Gary Allison and William Bast [annotated], September 23, 1983 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Second draft teleplay, part two by William Bast, from a story by Charles Gary Allison and William Bast [annotated], September 23, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Second draft teleplay, part two by William Bast, from a story by Charles Gary Allison and William Bast, September 23, 1983-October 24, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Second draft teleplay, part one by William Bast, from a story by Charles Gary Allison and William Bast [annotated], October 10, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Second draft teleplay, part one by William Bast, from a story by Charles Gary Allison and William Bast, October 10, 1983-October 24, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Collated shooting script, part one by William Bast, from a story by Charles Gary Allison and William Bast [annotated], November 23, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Revised first draft teleplay, part one by William Bast, from a story by Charles Gary Allison and William Bast [annotated], June 22, 1983-December 10, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Agreements, 1983-1985 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Call sheets, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Publicity, 1983-1984 (Box 20, Folder 4)
      Includes: clippings; press kits.
    - Research, undated (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Script notes, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Shooting schedules, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Writers Guild of America, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - The Fugitive (ABC, 1963-1967)
    - Second draft teleplay "Wanted: Someone to Drive" [annotated], February 5, 1965; Significant insect damage. (Box 20, Folder 9)
      Includes outline [broadcast as "All the Scared Rabbits"].
    - Revised first draft teleplay "All the Scared Rabbits" by William Bast and Norman Lessing, from a story by Bill Bast, August 9, 1965-August 18, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - The Greatest Show on Earth (ABC, 1963-1964)
    - Outlines and notes (Box 21, Folder 1)
      Includes script notes from S.S. Schweitzer to Bob Rafelson.
    - Final draft teleplay "Silent Love, Secret Love", January 3, 1963 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Incomplete first draft teleplay "Gent of the Year", May 6, 1963 (Box 21, Folder 3)
      It is unclear if this script was produced.
    - First draft teleplay "The Night the Monkey Died", January 20, 1964-January 28, 1964 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - The Hamptons (ABC, 1983)
    - Treatment by William Bast and Paul Huson [annotated], January 22, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Treatment by William Bast and Paul Huson, February 22, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Treatment by William Bast and Paul Huson [annotated], February 22, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Treatment by William Bast and Paul Huson [annotated], February 22, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Revised treatment by William Bast and Paul Huson, April 4, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - First draft teleplay "Episode One" by William Bast and Paul Huson [annotated], April 18, 1963 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Second draft teleplay "Episode One" by William Bast & Paul Huson [annotated], April 25, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Second draft teleplay "Episode One" by William Bast and Paul Huson, April 26, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Teleplay "Episode One" [no writer credited; annotated], undated (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Revised second draft teleplay pages "Episode One" by William Bast and Paul Huson, May 5, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Revised second draft teleplay "Episode One" by William Bast & Paul Huson, May 5, 1983-May 14, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Revised second draft teleplay "Episode One" by William Bast and Paul Huson, May 5, 1983-May 23, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - First draft teleplay "Episode Two" by Frank V. Furino [annotated], April 19, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Second draft teleplay "Episode Two" by Frank V. Furino, April 26, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Second draft teleplay "Episode Two" by Frank V. Furino, April 26, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Teleplay "Episode Two" [no writer credited; annotated], undated (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Revised second draft teleplay pages "Episode Two" by Frank V. Furino, from a story by William Bast and Paul Huson, May 5, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Revised second draft teleplay "Episode Two" by Frank V. Furino, from a story by William Bast & Paul Huson, May 5, 1983-May 14, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Revised second draft teleplay "Episode Two" by Frank V. Furino, from a story William Bast and Paul Huson, May 5, 1983-June 10, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - First draft teleplay "Episode Three" by Doris Silverton [annotated], undated (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Second draft teleplay "Episode Three" by Doris Silverton, Aopril 26, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Second draft teleplay "Episode Three" by Doris Silverton [annotated], April 26, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - Second draft teleplay "Episode Three" by Doris Silverton [annotated], April 26, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - Teleplay "Episode Three" [no writer credited; annotated], undated (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Revised second draft teleplay pages "Episode Three" by Doris Silverton, from a story by William Bast and Paul Huson, May 5, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Revised second draft teleplay "Episode Three" by Doris Silverton, from a story by William Bast & Paul Huson, May 5, 1983-May 14, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Revised second draft teleplay "Episode Three" by Doris Silverton, from a story by William Bast and Paul Huson [annotated], May 5, 1983-May 26, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Final draft teleplay "Episode Four" by Michael Russnow [annotated], April 25, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Second draft teleplay "Episode Four" by Michael Russnow [annotated], April 26, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Second draft teleplay "Episode Four" by Michael Russnow, Aopril 26, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Teleplay "Episode Four" [no writer credited; annotated], undated (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Revised second draft teleplay pages "Episode Four" by Michael Russnow, from a story by William Bast and Paul Huson, May 5, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Revised second draft teleplay "Episode Four" by Michael Russnow, from a story by William Bast & Paul Huson, May 5, 1983-May 14, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Revised second draft teleplay "Episode Four" by Michael Russnow, from a story by William Bast and Paul Huson [annotated], May 5, 1983-May 26, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - First draft teleplay "Episode Five" by Howard Lakin [annotated], April 19, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Revised draft teleplay "Episode Five" by Howard Lakin [annotated], April 26, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Second draft teleplay "Episode Five" by Howard Lakin [annotated], April 26, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Second draft teleplay "Episode Five" by Howard Lakin, Aopril 26, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - Teleplay "Episode Five" [no writer credited; annotated], undated (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - Revised second draft teleplay pages "Episode Five" by Howard Lakin, from a story by William Bast and Paul Huson, May 5, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Revised second draft teleplay "Episode Five" by Howard Lakin, from a story by William Bast & Paul Huson, May 5, 1983-May 14, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Revised second draft teleplay "Episode Five" by Howard Lakin, from a story by William Bast and Paul Huson [annotated], May 5, 1983-May 23, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Teleplay pages, May 18, 1983-June 10, 1983 [annotated] (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Agreements, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 4)
      Includes deal memos; annotated show bible.
    - Production, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 5)
      Includes de Forest Research reports; credit sheets; schedules.
    - Research, 1972-1983 (Box 24, Folder 6)
      Show bible for Family (ABC, 1976-1980) by Jay Presson Allen.
  - Hawaii Five-O (CBS, 1968-1980)
    - First draft teleplay "Anybody Can Build a Bomb", August 3, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 7)
      Includes treatments and research material.
    - First draft teleplay "Anybody Can Build a Bomb", August 30, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Final draft teleplay "Anybody Can Build a Bomb", September 6, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Final draft teleplay "Chain of Fire" by William Bast, from a story by William Bast and Tom Philbin, March 27, 1974 (Box 24, Folder 10)
      Broadcast as "A Hawaiian Nightmare."
  - Honey West (ABC, 1965-1966)
    - Revised teleplay "The Owl and the Eye", May 18, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Teleplay "Whatever Lola Wants...", July 21, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 2)
      Includes outlines.
  - Honeymoon Suite (ABC, 1972)
    - Second draft teleplay "The Night the Walls Came Tumbling Down", January 10, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 3)
      This script may have been unproduced.
  - It Takes a Thief (ABC, 1968-1970)
    - Teleplay "The Suzie Solitaire Caper"", March 21, 1969 (Box 25, Folder 4)
      Broadcast as "The Suzie Simone Caper."
    - Teleplay "The Scorpio Drop", October 15, 1969 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - ITV Play of the Week (ITV, 1955-1974)
    - Play script "The Myth Makers", 1960 (Box 25, Folder 6)
      Photocopied excerpt from Six Granada Plays (London: Faber and Faber), an anthology of television scripts adapted for the stage.
    - Rehearsal script "Tiger at the Gate" by Jean Giradoux, translated by Christopher Fry, and adapted for television by William Bast, July 4, 1960 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Camera script "Tiger at the Gate" by Jean Giradoux, translated by Christopher Fry, and adapted for television by William Bast, July 27, 1960 (Box 25, Folder 8)
      Includes clippings.
  - James Dean (NBC, 1976)
    - Story outline [annotated], January 24, 1975-February 27, 1975 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - First draft teleplay [annotated], May 14, 1975 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Revised first draft teleplay [annotated], May 29, 1975 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Second draft teleplay, June 16, 1975 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Revised second draft teleplay, July 25, 1975 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Final draft teleplay, September 26, 1975 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Revised final draft teleplay, October 27, 1975 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Revised final draft teleplay [annotated], October 27, 1975 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Revised final draft teleplay, October 27, 1975-November 10, 1975 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Revised final draft teleplay, October 27, 1975-November 20, 1975 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Final shooting script, November 17, 1975 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Master script [annotated], October 27, 1975-January 9, 1976 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Revised final draft teleplay, October 27, 1975-January 26, 1976 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Revised and amended teleplay [annotated], January 26, 1976 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Final shooting script [annotated], November 17, 1975-January 26, 1976 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Biography, 1956 (Box 27, Folder 7)
      James Dean by William Bast (New York: Ballantine, 1956) [three photocopied copies, one lightly annotated].
    - Calendars, 1975-1976 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Gilmore, Jonathan - cassette tape, undated (Box 28, Folder 2)
      FOLDER CONTAINS AUDIOVISUAL MATERIALS: Audiovisual materials in this folder will require assessment and possible digitization for safe access. To review these audiovisual materials, you must notify the UCLA Library Special Collections Reference Desk in advance of your visit.
    - Legal, 1975-1976 (Box 28, Folder 3)
      Includes writer's agreements.
    - Photographs, undated (Box 28, Folder 4)
      Includes scene stills; off-camera shots; publicity portraits; photos of William Bast and Lindsay Wagner.
    - Publicity, 1976 (Box 28, Folder 5-6)
      Includes clippings; lyrics to theme song by Frank Hlopcik and Bill Bast.
  - The Law and Mr. Jones (ABC, 1960-1962)
    - Teleplay "No News Is Good News" [annotated], February 6, 1962 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Teleplay "C'est la Show Biz", March 22, 1962 (Box 28, Folder 8)
      Includes outline and research material.
  - The Legend of Lizzie Borden (ABC, 1975)
    - Treatments "Lizzie Borden Took an Ax" [annotated], February 25, 1972-January 31, 1973 (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - First draft production mockup, July 12, 1974 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - First draft teleplay, August 14, 1974 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - First draft teleplay [illustrated], August 14, 1974 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Second draft teleplay, September 10, 1974 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Revised second draft teleplay [annotated], September 11, 1974 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Second draft teleplay, September 13, 1974 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Second draft teleplay, September 25, 1974 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Final draft teleplay, October 18, 1974 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Final draft teleplay, October 18, 1974-October 28, 1974 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Final draft teleplay [annotated], October 18, 1974-October 28, 1974 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - ABC notes, 1973-1974 (Box 30, Folder 3)
      Includes report from Standards and Practices.
    - Call sheets, 1974 (Box 30, Folder 4)
      Includes call sheets for other productions being shot at Paramount: Mandingo, Mannix, The Odd Couple, Happy Days, Little House on the Prairie, F. Scott Fitzgerald in Hollywood.
    - Clippings, 1975 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence and ephemera, 1974-1975 (Box 30, Folder 6)
      Includes typed and handwritten notes [badly damaged]; two handwritten letters from Gloria Stuart, who had her first role in almost thirty years here; material from the Society of the Friends of Lizzie Borden, part of the Unicorn Hunters of Lake Superior State College.
    - Legal, 1972-1975 (Box 30, Folder 7)
      Includes correspondence regarding litigation over the genesis of the project and of competing ones; agreements.
    - Research material, 1893-1974 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - The Long, Hot Summer (ABC, 1965-1966)
    - First draft teleplay "Home Is a Nameless Place", June 1, 1965 (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Final teleplay "Home Is a Nameless Place", August 2, 1965 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Love Story (NBC, 1973-1974)
    - First draft teleplay "The Roller Coaster Stops Here" by Michele Williams and William Bast, August 20, 1973 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Revised first draft teleplay "The Roller Coaster Stops Here" by Michele Williams and William Bast, August 20, 1973-August 26, 1973 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Second draft teleplay "The Youngest Lovers" by William Bast and Stephen & Elinor Karpf, from a story by Stephen & Elinor Karpf, October 18, 1973 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Shooting script "The Youngest Lovers" by Stephen & Elinor Karpf and William Bast [annotated], October 25, 1973-November 1, 1973 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - The Man in the Iron Mask (NBC, 1977)
    - Step outline [annotated], August 18, 1975 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - First draft teleplay from the story by Alexandre Dumas, October 20, 1975 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - First draft teleplay from the novel by Alexandre Dumas [annotated], October 12, 1975 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - First draft teleplay from the novel by Alexandre Dumas [annotated], October 20, 1975 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - First draft teleplay (long ending) from the novel by Alexandre Dumas, October 23, 1975 (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - First draft teleplay from the novel by Alexandre Dumas [annotated], October 23, 1975 (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Teleplay from the novel by Alexandre Dumas, undated (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Master script from the story by Alexandre Dumas [annotated by Mike Newell], October 20, 1975 (Box 32, Folder 2)
      Includes memo from Standards and Practices.
    - Final draft teleplay based on the stories by Alexandre Dumas, June 22, 1976-June 28, 1976 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Revised final draft teleplay based on the stories by Alexandre Dumas, July 7, 1976 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Shooting script based on the stories by Alexandre Dumas, July 7, 1976, with undated changes (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Clippings and publicity, 1976-1977 (Box 32, Folder 6)
      Includes program for the 1976-1977 Emmy Awards.
    - Correspondence, 1975-1977 (Box 32, Folder 7)
      Includes script notes; note from Mike Newell.
    - Legal, 1975-1977 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Novel, 1991 (Box 33, Folder 1)
      Contains The Man in the Iron Mask by Alexandre Dumas (Oxford: Oxford University Press, 1991).
    - Production, 1976 (Box 33, Folder 2)
      Includes shooting schedule
    - United Artists, 1997 (Box 33, Folder 3)
      Contains revised final shooting script by Randall Wallace, 4/4/97-7/21/97.
    - Writers Guild of America, 1997-1998 (Box 33, Folder 4)
      Contains material regarding whether William Bast should receive credit on United Artists' 1998 film adaptation.
  - The Man Who Never Was (ABC, 1966-1967)
    - First draft teleplay "All That Lia Ever Wanted", May 16, 1966 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Teleplay "Fall from a Shooting Star", June 10, 1966 (Box 33, Folder 6)
      It is unclear if this was produced, or what its broadcast title might have been.
    - Teleplay "Desperate Hours" by William Bast from a story by Edmund Morris, September 3, 1966-September 5, 1966 (Box 33, Folder 7)
      Probably broadcast as "Target: Eva."
  - The Manhunter (CBS, 1974-1975)
    - First draft teleplay "Mother Hen Gang", July 1, 1974 (Box 33, Folder 8)
      Broadcast as "The Ma Gantry Gang."
    - Final draft teleplay "The Ma Gantry Gang", July 16, 1974 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - The Master of Ballantrae (CBS, 1984)
    - Story outline, May 17, 1982 (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - Story outlines [annotated], May 17, 1982 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - First draft teleplay [annotated], August 1, 1982 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - First draft teleplay, August 1, 1982 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Second draft teleplay [annotated], September 7, 1982 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Second draft teleplay, September 7, 1982 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Second draft teleplay [annotated], September 7, 1982 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Second draft teleplay [annotated], September 7, 1982 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Second draft teleplay, September 7, 1982-September 14, 1982 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Revisions as given to typist, August 19, 1983 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Second draft teleplay, August 19, 1983 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Teleplay pages, September 14, 1982-August 23, 1983 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Clippings, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, 1983 (Box 35, Folder 8)
      Includes agreements.
    - Notes, 1982 (Box 35, Folder 9)
      Includes script notes from Douglas Hickox and CBS Standards and Practices.
    - Novel, 1902 (Box 36, Folder 1)
      The Master of Ballantrae by Robert Louis Stevenson (New York: P.F. Collier & Son) [photocopy]
    - Novel [annotated], 1902 (Box 36, Folder 2)
      Contains The Master of Ballantrae by Robert Louis Stevenson (New York: Charles Scribner's Sons) [photocopy]
    - Production, 1983 (Box 36, Folder 3)
      Contains: cast list; schedules.
  - Mistress of Paradise (ABC, 1981)
    - Step outline "Southern Gothic Tale" [annotated], December 12, 1979 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - First draft teleplay "The Second Mrs. Balford" [annotated], January 22, 1980 (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - First draft teleplay "The Second Mrs. Balford" [annotated], January 22, 1980 (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Revised first draft teleplay "Black Bayou" [annotated], January 30, 1980 (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - First draft teleplay "Black Bayou" [annotated], January 31, 1980 (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - First draft teleplay "Black Bayou", January 31, 1980 (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - Revised first draft teleplay "Black Bayou" [annotated], March 20, 1980 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Revised first draft teleplay "Black Bayou" [annotated], March 20, 1980 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Revised first draft teleplay "Black Bayou", March 28, 1980 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Revised first draft teleplay "Black Bayou" [annotated], March 28, 1980 (Box 37, Folder 4)
      Includes script notes from Jud Kinberg.
    - Second draft teleplay "Love's Savage Thrust" [annotated], May 7, 1980 (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - Second draft teleplay "The Dark Secret of Black Bayou", May 9, 1980 (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Revised second draft teleplay "The Dark Secret of Black Bayou" by Bennett Foster, April 6, 1981 (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - Final draft teleplay "The Dark Secret of Black Bayou" by Bennett Foster, May 26, 1981-June 22, 1981 (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - General, 1981 (Box 38, Folder 3)
      Includes notes on index cards, notice of tentative writing credits; reviews.
  - Mod Squad (ABC, 1968-1973)
    - Teleplay "The Girl in Chair Nine", May 19, 1969-May 22, 1969 (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - Teleplay "A Is for Annie", June 1, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - Teleplay "A Is for Annie", June 17, 1970-June 18, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - National Velvet (NBC, 1960-1962)
    - Teleplay "The Clown" by Pat Falken Smith and William Bast, from a story by William Bast, November 20, 1961 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - The New Perry Mason (CBS, 1973-1974)
    - Final teleplay "The Case of the Violent Valley", May 29, 1973 (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - Outlines and notes for "The Case of the Royal Rip-off", February 20, 1973-August 30, 1973 (Box 38, Folder 9)
      Includes handwritten step outlines; copy of a letter from William Bast to Ernie [Frankel?] detailing his work on the script, which had been disrupted because of the WGA strike.
    - First draft teleplay "The Case of the Royal Rip-off", July 16, 1973 (Box 38, Folder 10)
    - Second draft teleplay "The Case of the Royal Rip-off", undated (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - The Outer Limits (ABC, 1963-1965)
    - Treatment "Moonstone" by Lou Morheim and Joseph Stefano, undated (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Teleplay "Moonstone" by William Bast, from a story by Lou Morheim and Joseph Stefano, August 12, 1963 (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Second revised teleplay "Moonstone" by William Bast, from a story by Lou Morheim and Joseph Stefano, August 27, 1963 (Box 39, Folder 3)